Guide to the North American Coalition for Christianity and Ecology Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Material, 1987-2007; Series VIII
  - Documentation from related organizations, 1989-2007
    - Grassroots Evangelical Environmental Network (formerly Evangelical Environmental Network, Christian Society of the Green Cross, International Green Cross), 1990-1998 (Box 22, Folder 264)
    - International Coordinating Committee on Religion and the Earth, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 265)
    - Land Stewardship Council of North Carolina, 1992-1996 (Box 22, Folder 266)
    - Minnesota Earth Sabbath Team, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 267)
    - Minnesota Interfaith Ecology Coalition, 1991-2007 (Box 22, Folder 268)
    - National Religious Partnership for the Environment, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 269)
    - North American Conference on Religion and Ecology, 1989-1994 (Box 22, Folder 270)
    - Presbyterians for Restoring Creation, 1995-2000 (Box 22, Folder 271)
    - Program on Corporations, Law and Democracy, 1996-2005 (Box 22, Folder 272)
    - Religious Campaign for Forest Conservation, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 273)
    - St. Paul Covenant Ministry Council, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 274)
    - Vision Paper, 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 275)
  - Resources from outside NACCE, 1988-2000
    - Outside publications: various quotables, 1997 - ? (Box 23, Folder 276)
    - Resources, 1987-2000 (Box 23, Folder 277-278)
    - Resources: Catholicism and the environment, 1988-1994 (Box 23, Folder 279)
    - Resources: God's Earth Our Home, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 280)
    - Resources: Sabbath for the Environment, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 281)
  - Other documents associated with individuals, 1989-1997
    - Campbell, Cynthia, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 282)
    - Johnson, Al, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 283)
    - Massey, Marshall, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 284)
    - Ostrom, Karl, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 285)
    - Rae, Eleanor, 1989-1993 (Box 23, Folder 286)
    - Schaef, Finley: retirement celebration journal, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 287)